<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ugo Giocanti</title>
    <link>https://ugoue.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ugo Giocanti</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:17:37 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ugoue.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interlab football tournament</title>
      <link>https://ugoue.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:17:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ugoue.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://ugoue.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:17:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ugoue.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research interests Most of my research is in Graph theory, but I am also very interested in problems lying at the intersection of graph theory and other areas. In particular, I like concepts related to geometric group theory, coarse geometry or topology.
A few topics I (am trying to) work on: Cayley graphs, geometric group theory, canonical tree-decompositions, twin-width, universal covering, evasiveness of graph properties, fractional colouring of graphs, diameter-degree problem, group tilings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching (in french)</title>
      <link>https://ugoue.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:17:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ugoue.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>2023-2024  Conception et Exploitation des Bases de Données
Cours de niveau L3 Informatique. Cours de bases de données, qui fait suite à un premier cours en L2 de bases de données. TPs en SQL. Projet en SQL+Python.
Responsables du cours: Mario Cortes-Cornax.  2022-2023   Operation Research
Cours de niveau M1 Informatique. Chargé de TD.
Responsable du cours: Nadia Brauner.
  INF303: Modélisation des structures informatiques
Cours de niveau L2 Informatique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short CV</title>
      <link>https://ugoue.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ugoue.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I obtained my master in fundamental computer science in 2019 at the ENS de Lyon (France).
From September 2021 to September 2024, I was a PhD student in the Combinatorial Optimization team of G-SCOP laboratory in Grenoble (France), under the supervision of Louis Esperet, and the co-supervision of Stéphan Thomassé. I defended my PhD in Grenoble on the 9th of July 2024. I am now currently a postdoctoral research fellow supervised by Piotr Micek at the Jagiellonian university in Kraków (Poland)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>